<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<blog>
<post>
	<date>1336506043</date>
	<title>Imagine was a success!</title>
	<content>
	<p>We met the public and got their opinions on what they would like to track using Emp 
	and the <a href="plugintally.php">results</a> pretty much speak for themselves. It 
	seems like Social networking was high on the list like we knew it would be, but Home 
	Automation and Security were just as high if not higher.
	</p>
	
	<p>So it looks like our first round of plugins to tackle will be social networking. 
	But some promising leads were presented that I'd like to mention. We will be looking
	into X10 Home automation among other hardware as we were pleased to be able to talk 
	to a gentleman who worked for them. We will also be looking more closely at facial
	recognition and security related plugins soon as well.
	</p>
	
	<p>Whats next for Emp? Well, we want to get the core cleaned and polished for release.
	Therefore, next on the agenda is to get the Plugin API and Interface API formalized and 
	up on the website. (Although if you want to see our working API repo, please 
	<a href="mailto:dev@emp-d.com">email dev</a>.) Next, we will release an alpha version of 
	the framework along with some example interfaces to hopefully spark a bit more interest.
	As of now, we do not have a release date as two of we are in finals crunch week and will
	have our heads buried in books. 
	</p>
	
	<p>We will keep everyone informed that has <a href="signup.php">submitted their emails</a> 
	and will post on this blog as well. Please make sure you watch us on 
	<a href="http://github.com/empd">Github</a>, as we will release the API and source code 
	there.
	</p>
	
	<p>Thanks again,<br/>Emp Group</p>
	</content>
</post>

<post>
	<date>1336194000</date>
	<title>Emp has launched!</title>
	<content>
        <p>Welcome to the Emp website, we plan on updating you as the day progresses to 
        let you know how <a href="http://rit.edu/imagine">Imagine RIT</a> is going! But 
        please feel free to stop by if you are in the area. We will be explaining the uses 
        and taking ideas for possible plugins. We will be keeping a running list and tally 
        here: <a href="pluginlist.php">Plugin Tally</a>.
        </p>

        <p>Please look around our website to get more information, we will also be online
        during Imagine taking and answering questions on our freenode channel <em>#emp-dev</em> and
        <em>#emp-help</em>. You can join either channel and chat from our website on our 
        <a href="contact.php">Contact</a> page.
        </p>

    
        <p>While you are here, whether you are at Imagine or not, consider tweeting your
        ideas to <a href="http://twitter.com/emp_dev">@emp_dev</a> as well. We are looking
        for popular online or offline services that you use often that you would like a 
        monitoring system to supervise for you. For examples of some uses, check out our
        <a href="about.php">About page</a>.
        </p>

        <p>To sign up for updates, you can either watch our 
        <a href="http://github.com/empd">Github page</a> for development updates, or enter 
        your email address on our <a href="signup.php">Sign up</a> page for release updates.
        </p>
	</content>
</post>
</blog>